if someone had told me 24 years ago that
this former hip-hop artist would be at a
Daniel 11 conference I've been like
you're crazy what are you smoking it's a
privilege to be with you today I believe
that Jesus is coming again better amen
okay let's pray and let's get into the
word Heavenly Father I want to ask your
blessing upon your people Lord send your
angels to give us understanding this we
pray in Jesus name Amen the Bible tells
us Jesus himself says that I am the
center of the scriptures he says the
scriptures testify of me and I believe
that when we approach the Book of Daniel
we should approach it in this sense
Jesus says all the Scriptures testify of
him let me give you one example quickly
even in those places where we think
Jesus is not there he is that Christ is
on every page of the Bible there's a
story in the Old Testament of a man by
the name of David who commits adultery
and and has Bathsheba's husband Uriah
killed you know that story and the Bible
tells us that that as David thinks he
gets away with this but the Prophet
comes to him and says you have sinned
remember Bathsheba is pregnant yes
and so David repents praise God
however however the Prophet says to him
you you will live because you repented
but the child that you have that your
your wire that Bathsheba's gonna have is
gonna die unfair story how many of you
say unfair story yes haven't you read
that story before and said Wow why would
God punish the child so listen we don't
know who this child is the child doesn't
have a name all we know is that it was a
male child mean
the child was the son of David McCoy I
was gonna wingman the son of David was
brought into this world because of
someone else's sin and died that someone
else might live Christ's beloved is the
center of the Scriptures amen
and the same is true in the book of
Daniel